Fighting Hengtian with different boyfriends and the same military commander,
Then my boyfriend called his other girlfriend over.
So how would I deal with my three boyfriends and a love rival with the emotional intelligence of a military general?
Because you three will take turns being my husband. I'll be the first to go, I'll be the first to go,
I'll be your first boyfriend. You've beaten the dog, I'm here.
I am your boyfriend’s girlfriend, right? Yes, a wrench is a gun.
From the Yehedala Gang.
Beijing Huang Tenggen'er, husband, it hasn't started yet, let's start! There are more than thirty fans left in the room,
As a jury, let’s see how many points the five generals can score for their emotional intelligence! Ah, hello,
Sister Azhen! Hello, hello, Xiaojiu, right? Ah, yes! Wait a minute,
I pulled my husband down. Is my brother-in-law coming too? Sister, yes! hello, hello, hello, brother-in-law,
Hello brother-in-law! Hello, my husband is the best Veyron player I have ever seen! Damn,
Then let me come to Luna, brother. I feel like I can learn one-tenth of what I learned from you.
I even feel like I can conquer the entire industry! Real or fake? It’s true, brother! Brother,
I brought you nine rounds of A-size bullets. I brought them to you. I wish my brother-in-law love, I wish my sister this love,
I wish the love between my sister and my brother-in-law is like a big bullet and a big bullet, which can lead to thousands of miles of space travel.
A big A will always be connected. Brother-in-law and sister are not as affectionate as me. I have only seen them in movies.
I have seen Juliet and Romeo, Juliet and Romeo.
Find one, find one, baby! I’m so strong, brother Niu! I'm not strong, hide behind me, baby!
I see someone, come and grab it! Slow down, slow down, brother-in-law! This is the most European and American dragon I have ever seen with a three-section axis.
No, because my baby is here! You are worthy of being my master. I have to learn from you, brother-in-law!
How do you learn this, baby? I want to eat! Will you marry me at the space base? ah! Propose?
Brother-in-law? This is a battlefield! I'm going! battlefield!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
to you,baby,you,you,baby,to you,
that's too much, that's too much,
This explosion-proof old handsome armor is very handsome, brother. How do you say that? Brother, old handsome armor with explosion-proof head,
My marksmanship is quite accurate! Yeah? You, you, you, this old handsome guy with an explosion-proof head look like you have strength,
He looks handsome! I look handsome with any gun. Where did you find such a good boyfriend, sister? Ah,
I am from Jining, Shandong. What? Sister, let me tell you, Shandong men love girls the most. Really,
Brother-in-law, I have seen this Veyron like you before.
The lightning stock and phantom hammer, which are the top and best in thinking and marksmanship, are really beyond the reach of ten thousand of me.
I tell the truth. Yeah? I don't like to understand. Who wants to ask me how good my Veyron will be in the future?
I just said I learned it from my brother-in-law. Baby, I ordered Malatang for you, and added more tofu skin and folded ear root.
Give me some Malatang quickly! Sister, do you still eat Zheergen? sister? Ah, yes,
I went to Haidilao in our county and smelled the Zheergen before. It was so fishy that I couldn't put it down. Malatang,
I will eat whatever my baby likes to eat. My uncle, brother-in-law.
You are such a hot guy! Just be envious! I can't play anymore, I'm leaving on a business trip.
Where are you going on a business trip? Well, let’s go to Europe! Oh, what kind of play style is that in Europe? Better than Europe and America?
Is it more ruthless than Europe and America? elder brother! Brother, when the time comes, you will learn to teach me how to play European style, brother!
You want to rule the earth, Xiaojiu! No, no, no, sister, I just need to rule the aerospace industry, sister.
Can I post your wedding photos on TikTok later?
May your family be blessed with money? So happy! So happy! Oops, then I’m leaving,
I'm going to catch a plane, baby.
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye, master,
bye bye bye bye, this one has five, I will take you to Europe and the United States, brother-in-law.
Uh, wait a minute, wait a minute, I'll take my husband and brother-in-law and leave them to me. Don't you want to fight in Europe?
Husband, why did you come here? Do you want two more fights? Wife, who did you fight just now? Fuck,
More than nine million have been paid out! We were lining up for a passerby just now. That passerby was stupid, right, Xiaojiao?
Uh, wait a minute, I just struck, strike, kill! Is he a passerby, Xiaojiu? Wait a minute,
Wait a minute, I, I, I will go to Douyin sister, wait, wait, it doesn’t seem right, I sent it wrong,
Wrong message, sister! Okay, okay, okay. Oh, passers-by! If it weren't for that passerby,
I can earn 20 million, right, Xiaojiu? ah! Ah, yes, yes, sister, the passers-by we just lined up,
Everyone comes to that Veyron, that Veyron is stupid, but my husband Veyron is the most powerful.
Right, husband? If not, then I'll play Luna. I feel like I can learn one-tenth of what I learned from you.
I feel like I can fly all over space. Oops, no, no, no, I also eat sour food. Daddy,
My big daddy, I’m fast! I'll pull the string for you, brother, you're so strong! Brother, holy shit, you’re so strong! Brother,
Awesome brother, why are you so strong? Why not? It's just because you didn't come, the passerby is stupid. Oops,
Then I almost didn't come out. Well, right, miss? What's wrong, brother?
That passerby just now, let’s live like a boss! He takes us to the central control. Let’s finish the central control.
He took us to the dormitory and then to the Fourth University. Yes, it is far different from my baby. Yes, yes, yes,
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on! This horse is signed by Julang. Yes, there is also that huge wave,
Then the passerby who got on the horse didn't even know how to use the giant wave. Ah, here you come to draw bags, draw bags for Xiu'er, right, miss?
What kind of lightning gun butt did the passerby use just now? Phantom grip? It's like shooting a gun and having Parkinson's disease. Yes, that's right.
My brother-in-law has to modify the gun, C T stock, uh, attack grip.
Then from now on, I will be hairless and not like the passerby just now. From now on, you will be my master.
This is the most European and American dragon I have ever seen with a three-section axis. Oh, this is my baby that I want to hold.
Don't ask me how good my Veyron will be in the future, I'll just say that I learned it from my brother-in-law. Wife,
Will you marry me at the space base? Ah, no one has ever proposed to me at the space base. Yes,
No, I'm serious.
Let’s just let it go with you. So many people are enjoying themselves over this. Enjoy! Oh, baby,
If you don’t promise me, don’t eat hi! Xiaojiu, come and take a wedding photo for us two. What wedding photo are you taking?
How to shoot? I haven't taken any pictures, brother. Yeah? Well, I just contacted someone who took wedding photos on Douyin. ah!
Ah, brother-in-law, brother-in-law, move a little to the right, look a little sweeter, and protect your eyes. OK,
Is it handsome enough? Hey, that Veyron is so ugly, isn’t it, Xiaojiu? Let me tell you, brother-in-law.
Just take a Navero, that one with an anti-explosion head, old League One, hey, my marksmanship is a bit bad,
Give him a machine gun to kill, haha, that's too far, brother, it's the first time I've been ranked like this. Ah,
Yes, yes, where did you find such a good boyfriend? Sister, I want to find one too, can’t you hear this?
From Henan? From Anyang, Henan? Henan people are the most loving people, and they love girls the most, right? Ah,
When the time comes, you come to my old Anyang, and I’ll treat you to eat here.
I don’t know how to cook food. I have to learn from you, brother-in-law. Ah, my wife,
I ordered your favorite Malatang, specially added with tofu skin and lotus root slices.
All you like to eat. I'm not very good. Did you forget to fold the ears, sister? Ah,
Don’t you like eating folded ear roots? I don’t eat it. I never eat the root of the fungus. you,
I don’t eat the root of Zheer. Don’t you want to eat Zheergen, sister? I don't want to eat it, eh. My wife-in-law loves to eat,
I know best.
I order spicy hotpot every day. Yes, yes, yes, did I remember correctly? Hahahahaha! Oops,
I'm at work, I'm going to eat, I'll pick it up, okay, then you can just eat and don't order me.
C U Lala, bye! Let me go! Let me go! Bye-Bye! Bye-Bye! Pay homage to the master! Sister, do you still want to fight?
Wait a minute, wait a minute, my husband is coming. Any more? Baby, do you miss me? Hello,
Hello, sister, hello, husband, why are you here? I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Who were you fighting just now?
I saw that restaurant, we ate more than five million, ha! Ah! We just played two games with passers-by, brother-in-law.
Hahahahaha! That's right, passers-by just queued up for two Veyrons to order food. Yes, yes!
Are you a mighty Dragon thief, brother? Yes, falling to the ground like this, I feel like I can learn one-tenth of what I learned from you.
I feel like I can fly all over space. Ha ha! It's over, baby, I have to go downstairs, I have to go downstairs.
OK, go ahead, baby. I'm going downstairs to pick up the express. I'll be up right away! Okay, okay!
There's no turning back, we both have to wait. OK, OK, then I'm leaving. OK.
Then go ahead, baby! Hey, brother, someone is probably here, brother!
I just saw the three people in your team, they are really the way to go in the lobby! Someone is coming, someone is coming, brother!
Brother, tell me the truth! Uh, my sister said to play two random games first,
Let's play together after you get off work. I can't help it, you are really so clingy, you have to wait for me to get off work every day,
Play two or three moves with me, and you will be mastered by me. You know what, brother? That's true,
Brother? Is that true, brother?
Tell me from the bottom of your heart, what do you think of your real sister? Sister Zhen even told me that she missed you.
He said that your Veyron was very good, and then he said that he would take a wedding photo for you later. Hey, no hair,
Your real sister just loves to go out and play, and she also loves to eat some spicy hotpot. Hey, yes, my sister loves Malatang. Yes,
Play a series of broadcasts, ten is not good, come back, baby. Oh, honey, you are finally back.
A eight here has been out for several times, and you are finally back, you. Hey, what do these two cuckolds mean?
Xiao Jia, ah, oh, don’t you understand this? This is to deceive the opponent A, honey, brother,
This brother and I have great ideas! Yeah? Yes, yes, yes, brother, you are too poisonous, brother,
He is the guy who tricked the opponent A into shooting bullets. You didn't talk just now, not the baby. Brother has been praising you just now.
Why don't you stop talking, honey? Let me tell you, how did this brother praise you back then?
The sky is full of excitement. Yes, oops, that’s what my baby is like! Holy shit, what a guy! I have a plan, let’s go.
This gun is so powerful bro! come on! Slow down, slow down! Be good,
This is the most European and American dragon I have seen since the third quarter. Am I that cruel? Baby, you don’t even know,
The two passers-by in the row above me are stupid. They don’t really know anything. They just like to use those two to break the huge waves.
That wheelchair gun is really not as good as Brother’s M7. Really, let’s be honest, is it so crazy?
Husband, I don’t want to play anymore. I have to go to bed. You and Xiaojiu can play. Sister, don’t you want to play anymore? Sister?
ospace
Ah, this, uh, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute, what are you doing? What dad cooks is not an ordinary dish.
Oh my god! Ah, then I will protect you, husband. Wait a minute, I I I I I take a break,
I'll take a break. This guy's sister-in-law is looking for someone, uh, sister-in-law, sister-in-law, sister-in-law, sister-in-law, hello, hello,
Little baby. Oops, hubby, come and get it, take out the oil! Oops, am I out of gas? Sister, sister, sister,
I'm practicing, sister.
Who is the green one? Hey, sister, I, I, I, I am the keyboard again, sister. The baby comes with a flight box and insurance.
The keyboard, haha, don’t want the green one. The passerby who scanned the code sign was very stupid and very shady. Was he using it?
It’s time to recharge the energy bar, brother. Haha, don't be numb. Wow, hubby, hurry up and get it, hubby,
Have you eaten the Malatang I just ordered for you? After I finished eating, I loved the spicy soup.
You drink it secretly on the roadside, right, Littlefoot? Uh, haven't you eaten, brother? ah! My brother said that Zheergen is particularly delicious.
Also added bean curd and lotus root slices? Well, yes, yes! ah!
Why did you bring a bunch of headphones in? What is this for? I'm playing, I'm playing with me,
Confuse the sister opposite. This is useless! I brought in a spare one to use on my back, sister.
Then you and my husband can take the remaining two. Hey, wait.
Wait a minute! Wait a moment! I was out of control when I fired the lightning at 18, so I had to get off quickly.
The old man downstairs gave me a three-wheel shave. I had to leave quickly, leave quickly, leave quickly! Let me go!
Let me go! Well, brother, why don’t you wait a moment? Evacuate immediately, brother! Hey, no, brother,
I just bought these three wheels, and I just bought them second-hand. I have to keep an eye on them, you know? Well, okay,
Baby, no, I'm leaving! Bye-Bye! Bye-Bye! Then bye! Bye, brother!
What did you mean by giving me the headset just now, brother Xiaojiu? Uh, why don't you stop beating me next time, sister-in-law? Hey,
I've seen it a long time ago. You might be hinting at me, right?
Uh, Xiao Jiujiu lied to me about this! I have three children, and seven boys have met their parents.
I have dated sixteen boyfriends and I haven’t told him anything and I don’t know anything. And ah,
Your brother also promised me 1.68 million to marry me! OK, OK, OK, he’s just a bit cool.
Brother, how about you take me to eat 1.68 million? Me me me? Sister, brother,
Do you mean that a car has had its engine replaced three times, been involved in seven accidents, and has been transferred sixteen times?
This time it’s 1.68 million, right?
I, the last part is our fan rating session,
There were actually twenty-seven people who rated the general’s emotional intelligence above eight points! I want to score eight points,
That is, if I encounter this kind of suffocating fists, I will feel suffocated in my stomach. Hey,
This brother was calm and didn't say anything, so I'll give it an eight-point rating! But when it comes to reality, I tell the truth,
I have to beat him. However, all the judges in the professional group gave it a zero score.
Because he just needs to provide that emotional value and base.
That's enough. Then he used the headphone head and the disrespectful one at the end.
Just zero points, okay? So how many points do you think this military commander should be given for his emotional intelligence?